[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Qigong, which is recommended in traditional Chinese medicine, is what type of exercise?", "correct_answer": "Breathing", "incorrect_answers": ["Wrestling", "Weightlifting", "Swimming"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is it true that in the movie The Great Escape, Donald Pleasence played Lt. Colin Blythe known as the Forger?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Star Wars character on the Dark Side has a double lightsaber?", "correct_answer": "Darth Maul", "incorrect_answers": ["Count Dooku", "Emperor Palpatine", "Darth Vader"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1974 movie The Conversation dealt with several topics. Which of the following was not one of them?", "correct_answer": "tax cheating", "incorrect_answers": ["paranoid individuals", "electronic surveillance", "corporate power"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This religion encourages vegetarianism.", "correct_answer": "Buddhism", "incorrect_answers": ["Islam", "Shintoism", "Christianity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Homeless people in the film The Pursuit of Happyness were played by actual homeless people.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1960 movie Spartacus, the role of Roman general and politician Marcus Licinius Crassus was played by Peter Ustinov.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who made an assassination attempt on Ronald Reagan?", "correct_answer": "John Hinckley, Jr.", "incorrect_answers": ["James Brady", "Lee Harvey Oswald", "Jack Ruby"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the favorite food of the Fairy-bluebird, which is found only in Asia?", "correct_answer": "Figs", "incorrect_answers": ["Goji berries", "Grasshoppers", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Gothams main newspaper in the movie Batman?", "correct_answer": "The Gotham Globe", "incorrect_answers": ["The Gotham Herald", "The Gotham Times", "The Gotham Gazette"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The \u2018Scotch Whisky Act 1988\u2019 legally defines Scotch whisky. Which of these is the standard that whisky must meet in order to be called, Scotch Whisky?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["It must be distilled at a Scottish distillery.", "It must have an alcoholic strength of less than 94.8% by volume.", "It must be matured in Scotland in oak casks for not less than three years."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A fly flies slower when the sun is behind the clouds.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]